recovery one of the most crucial things
when it comes to Fitness is working out
that soreness from a heavy lifting day
and while going to see a massage
therapist is a great way to do that you
know that could be pretty pricey over
time percussive massage guns offer some
of the same benefits while also cutting
back on that price I've been using the
hyper risk hypervolt go-to for quite a
while now and so today I'm going to
share my experience with y'all
[Music]
what's up everybody it's Jake that's
right you guessed it I'm back in the
Barb and garage gym with another review
ready to go for y'all this time though
I've got the hyper risk hypervolt go 2.
in this video I'm going to walk you
through everything you need to know
about this massage gun from the price
the features some pros and cons that
you'll most likely experience and of
course who should or maybe should not
buy one of these before I get going
though we've reviewed a good amount of
massage guns on barbin.com and if you
want to browse our best list just go and
search bar band best massage guns and
you can find out for yourself which ones
we like the best but also which one is
going to suit you the best
foreign
but if you aren't familiar with what a
percussive massage is well it's
basically a combination of rapid and
repetitive pressure mixed in with
vibrational therapy so the head of the
massage gun moves rapidly and it applies
enough Force to relieve any stiffness
that you might have in your soft tissues
so let's talk about portability
the hyperus hypervolt go to is extremely
portable it only weighs one and a half
pounds and as you can see the dimensions
are really small you can easily toss it
in your bag and go and plus it's
approved by the TSA for carry-on so you
can definitely take it on a plane with
you if you want to you have two
different attachment heads to throw onto
your massage gun this is going to allow
you to focus on large muscle groups and
also pinpoint specific areas if you
choose to do so the companion app is
also a great tool for anybody who does
not know how to properly use a massage
gun it's going to show you exactly how
to do that it's also going to provide
you with you know different routines
that you can do to unlock specific areas
on your body Plus Motor is relatively
quiet especially compared to some other
massage guns that I've used in my past
and just you know the other ones that
are available on the market
[Music]
now there's not a whole lot of Cons with
the hypervolt go-to but there's still a
couple that I need to mention you know
once again you only get two attachment
heads there's other ones out there that
feature five maybe even more so
obviously those are going to be a little
bit more versatile than this one is
right here there's also other massage
guns that feature up to 20 different
speed settings while the hypervolt go-to
only has three it's it's not that these
speed settings are not effective trust
me they are it's just that there's not
as much variety and lastly it's 200 you
know there's other ones out there that
are cheaper than the hypervolt go to and
they feature both more attachments and
more speed settings so it's kind of
something to consider as well
[Music]
all right so let's break down the price
now for the hyperus hypervolt go to
including shipping you're going to be
looking at spending right around 200 and
you can either purchase this directly
through hyper risk or you can even
purchase it through Rogue which is
actually where we got ours now 200 is
kind of pricey considering you only get
two attachment heads and three different
speed settings you know remember I just
spoke about how there's other ones out
there that are cheaper that feature more
attachments and more speed settings but
I gotta say this still packs a punch
I've been able to notice the effects on
my body and my sore muscles plus you can
easily toss it in your bag take it on
the road with you and you know like I
said it's TSA approved so if you're not
checking a bag or going on a trip you
know you just have a carry-on you can
just throw it in your carry-on bag and
you're good to go and then you know once
you compare using the hypervolt go to
you know compared to going to see a
massage therapist this once or twice a
week this is definitely going to pay for
itself in the long run
if you don't want to spend 200 up front
I really don't blame you I've talked
about it in the past with a lot of
products I don't like doing that either
luckily you can Finance your purchase
you'll be making monthly payments of
around 50 bucks so if you purchase this
massage gun through hyper risk directly
you can utilize klarna and if you were
to go with Rogue to buy the hypervolt
go-to you can utilize pay later from
PayPal
[Music]
so the companion app is one of my
favorite features one of my favorite
things that hyper is has to offer it's
going to be really nice as I said for
anybody who does not know how to
properly use a massage gun because it
provides you with guided sessions on how
to do so plus you know as you're making
a profile it's going to ask you what
activities you participate in that way
the app knows a little bit about you and
what to suggest for you specifically so
these activities range from running to
lifting even just you know sitting at a
desk all day long it's going to provide
you with a routines tab it's going to be
full of different exercises and routines
that you can do from unlocking your hips
to even you know relieving neck tension
from sitting at a desk all day long it
was a little odd though that there
weren't any routines or any specific
exercises for specific muscle groups
like your pecs your lats your abs and
even your upper back now I would imagine
those will be added in the not too
distant future but for now they're not
there which is definitely something
worth mentioning
[Music]
[Applause]
all right so let's talk about the build
now with the hypervolt go too starting
with the handle it's just over six
inches in diameter it's going to give
you a nice little surface area to hang
on to from the base of the handle to the
top of the massage gun just over seven
inches and without an attachment here
from front to back it's also just over
six inches the handle is at a bit of an
angle right here it's also wrapped in
rubber it's going to give you a nice
grip and you know that angle is going to
be really nice in terms of not wearing
out your wrist and your hand as you're
using the massage gun
it's made from a hard plastic as you can
hear and so are the attachments so they
might not be the most ideal thing in the
world for any sensitive areas such as
your hands it also only weighs one and a
half pounds so it's really easy to bring
it around town with you and you know
stash it in your bag and hit the road
all right so in terms of features you do
once again have two different attachment
heads to toss onto the hypervolt go to
the bullet right here is going to be
more so focused around you know
pinpointing a specific area as well as
deep tissue massages while this flat
head is going to be more so for large
muscle groups and more of a surface
level to medium level massage you do
have three different Outlet attachments
that you can take especially if you're
going you know overseas that's going to
be really nice for you and the power
button back here actually doubles as a
speed changer so to turn it on all you
do is press and hold for two seconds or
so
that's going to cut on you'll see this
light down here so this is going to
indicate how much battery life you have
so when it's green like this it's fully
charged over time it's going to switch
to yellow and then a bit of a yellow
orangish and then red as it's about to
die so the power button also doubles as
the speed changer so to do that
you'll just simply press the button
and you'll see these LED lights light up
and to do that I just press the button
and my two three press it again and it
cuts it off and to turn it the whole
thing off once again press and hold for
right around two seconds or so and it'll
shut off as you see so the battery is
built to last around three hours but
that's gonna change depending on what
speed setting you have it on and also
how hard you're pressing against your
body so if you have it on that highest
setting and you're pressing pretty hard
against you that's going to decrease
that battery life maybe around two hours
or so which is still pretty solid now if
the battery does die completely you can
expect it to take around three hours as
well to fully charge
all right so let's do a quick rundown on
how to properly use the hypervolt go to
I'm gonna start with how to charge it
you have a little charging port right
here this is a 18 volt charger just
simply plug it in
it's good to go really easy to do so now
I talked about you know these different
attachments right here if you decide to
travel overseas and you obviously want
to change your outlet all you do is
press it on this button rotate that it's
going to come right out and you can you
know whichever one you need
same exact process in reverse order it's
really easy to do so I mean it doesn't
take very long whatsoever now press the
power button for around two seconds hold
it in there
that green light is going to come on if
it is fully charged now we're going to
throw on the attachments now it's really
easy to do so it's just going to fit
right in here simply press it all the
way in there you'll tell you'll be able
to tell when it's all the way in there
now once again to change the speed
settings obviously we have it off we're
going to press this one time it's going
to be on that lowest speed setting
and to use it I mean just simply find
your target area
just move it around a little bit or
maybe pinpoint exactly where you want
specifically if you had that bullet head
attachment you know and a massage gun
like this you really don't have to press
too hard you can stall it
if you wanted to but you know like I
said you really don't have to press down
that hard and you know once again to go
up into higher speed it's just press the
button
and it's going to be right there and you
know as you can tell like yeah there's a
little bit of noise but it's expected
but it compared to some other ones out
there it's really not that loud
whatsoever I promise you and to stop it
press the button again and once again to
turn it off press and hold for around
two seconds now when it comes to using a
massage gun like this your target time
really needs to be around one to two
minutes I wouldn't go over two minutes
honestly especially if you're trying to
recover because if you go over that you
know you do run the risk of potential
injury and even bruising for an area
that's already injured and I don't think
you really want that now if you want to
use this to warm up I'd probably go
maybe no more than a minute that way you
know the blood flow is really rocking in
that area and you're nice and warmed up
to download the app all you need to do
is go to the App Store type in hyperus
you'll click you know you'll see it
you'll see the app open it up download
it and whenever you sign up originally
it's gonna have you fill out you know
frequent activities that you do in fact
participate in but for the sake of this
video I already have all my ends I'm
going to show you how to edit them so if
you go to profile and scroll down go to
accountant profile and you'll see
frequent activities click there and
you'll see all the different activities
you can choose from we got football
basketball office work I mean surfing
snowboarding really there's a lot of
different activities for you to choose
from right here so that's really cool
and once you have all that filled out
every time you open up the app click on
routines it's gonna pop up with top
rated most used
athletes you know there's a lot of
different things that you can go with
right here and if you click on body it's
going to show a diagram of a body and
that's going to allow you to click on
you know your forearms maybe your quads
your biceps really whatever and also
flip it around you know you got your
hamstrings you have your IT band and
your hips you know a bunch of different
things for you to work on here so let's
click on triceps click search routines
click on upper body Glide as you see
right here click on start right there
it's gonna pull up
it's going to show you exactly how to do
everything which is really nice shows
you exactly where to pinpoint it it does
have a video with a nice diagram of how
to do everything you can always pause it
like I just did in the session resume it
there's also a little thing right here
on the right and it's going to show you
the rest of the routine you're doing I
will say though
you know some of these attachments you
don't have with the hypervolt go to so
some of this stuff isn't going to be
compatible with this exact massage gun
[Music]
all right so who should purchase the
hyperus hypervolt go to well honestly I
think everybody can benefit from a
percussive massage gun such as this one
right here you know whether you know
you're sore from a long day at the gym
or a long day at the office our bodies
and muscles you know tend to get pretty
sore this is a great way to start
feeling like yourself again if you
travel a lot I really think you're going
to appreciate just how small the
hyperbolt go to is it only weighs one
and a half pounds you know it's not
heavy you're not gonna be lugging it
around the dimensions are relatively
small as well so you can easily toss it
in a bag and hit the road and plus it is
TSA approved for carry-on so if you're
one of those people who doesn't like to
check a bag as you're getting on a plane
you don't have to leave this at home
plus you do have a companion app you can
download so anybody who does not know
how to properly use a massage gun well
good news you're going to learn today or
really the day that you download the app
because it's going to provide you with
guided sessions on how to properly
relieve that stress in whatever muscle
group you're looking for
[Music]
okay so who should not purchase the
hypervolt go to well if you want your
massage gun to feature more than two
attachments and more than three speed
settings you can definitely find some
other ones out there you know some of
them like I said feature up to 20
different speed settings and over five
different attachments so they are a
little bit more versatile than the
hypervolt go 2 is plus there's a good
amount out there that are significantly
cheaper than the hypervolt go 2 is and
some of those also feature more
attachments and more speed settings so
definitely keep that in mind and if
you're one of those people who would
just rather go and see a massage
therapist you're probably not going to
be too interested in a massage gun like
this one all right that's a wrap on
today's review over the hyper risk
hypervolt go to I really enjoy just how
small this massage gun is I can easily
take it on the road with me and even
though it's small it still packs a bit
of a punch and I really like that
whether it be from a long day in the
weight room or a long day at the office
this is a really good good way to loosen
up any stiffness that you might have and
also it could be a good way for you to
get warmed up before a workout or a run
remember though there's only two
attachment heads and three different
speed settings with the hypervolt go-to
so you're definitely going to want to
keep that in mind when you're deciding
between this one and another one out
there on the market that has more of
both of those features at the end of the
day though I can't really speak on those
other Alternatives but I can speak on
the hypervolt go too and I gotta say
it's pretty effective I really
appreciate you all for watching I hope I
was able to answer some questions that
you might have over the hypers hypervolt
go to as always stay on the lookout for
my next review but for now head over to
barbin.com and you can read more about
this product right here just search bar
Bend hyperus hypervault go to review and
you can read over everything we
discussed here today I'll see y'all next
time
[Music]
foreign